MOHAMED AHMED ELGEADY

FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER 18/8/2002

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

i'am Mohamed Ahmed Frontend Web Developer and I have experience in the field of web development and design.

I always look forward to confrontation, challenge and thinking outside the box I strive to create beautiful and immersive web through carefully designed and user focused code instructions I am passionate and energetic as I can develop my skills and gain more experience.

CONTACT:

- +20 1065781321
- m16ahmed17@gmail.com
- Minyat SamannudAga, Ad Daqahliyah
- https://portfolioo-1.netlify.app
- https://github.com/Mohamed20a
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/ mohamed-ahmed-bb358b239/

EDUCATION:

Mansoura University

Faculty of Computer Science - Software Engineering

Apr 2020 - May 2024

(STUDENT)

SKILLS:

- Html/Html5
- Css/Css3
- Javascript
- React js
- ¡Query
- Bootstrab
- Experience With Git and Github

WORK EXPERIENCE

Head technical Committee in SLS Team

Web Developer

2022 - Present

Head technical Committee in SLS Team in Mansoura University

Front End Developer

2021 - Present

- More than a year of experience in front end
- Built and maintained websites for clients through various online platforms
- Assisted troubleshooting software.
- Created and tested applications for websites.
- Filed reports, gathered information, and performed research.

Soft Skills:

- Problem Solving
- Team Work
- Time management
- Stress management
- Creativity
- Self Learning
- Good in English